mylittlemuffin.com 2017-05-24

# Terms and Privacy policy » My Little Muffin

### Content provided on this site is for entertainment or informational purposes only and should not be construed as medical or health, safety, legal or financial advice.

### Medical Disclaimer

This website is for informational purposes only and is not a substitute for personal medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment.  Our goal is to provide accurate, timely, general information. However, some information may not be appropriate to your individual needs. Therefore, it is essential that you consult with your physician to determine what is appropriate for you.  No information or recommendations found on this site should be implemented before discussing with your own physician. Before performing Yoga, Pilates or any exercises, consult with your physician to determine whether the exercises are appropriate and safe for you.

### Privacy Policy

We at mylittlemuffin.com value you as a customer and we are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.  We collect information only when necessary to conduct our business, to advise you of our products and services, and to provide you with customer service. We will only use your personal data in a way that is fair to you.

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information that we gather when you use our Website or purchase our products or services.

### Information we may collect and how it might be shared

We may collect and maintain several types of customer information as needed for these purposes, such as the following:

From you, your name, and email address, as needed to fulfill your requests for our products and services. We will not sell or share this information with others.

From you, information needed for customer support or to respond to any queries you raise with us. We will not sell or share this information with others.

Aggregate data to analyze how our customers utilize our Website, including for example, browser information, mobile device type, pages requested, length of stay, and so forth. We may share this information with others to analyze how often and in what ways customers use our Website, but we will not share aggregate information with others in a manner that would identify you personally.

### Security

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You are responsible for selecting and protecting your password appropriately and protecting against access to your computer or device and browser.

Payment transactions will be through a third party and payment transactions will be encrypted by the third party. mylittlemuffin.com will not have access to your credit card information.

We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure the security of your personal information and to prevent unlawful or unauthorized access to your personal information. We store your personal information on a secure server with industry standard server security and firewalls.  However, we cannot guarantee complete security. The transmission of information via the Internet can never be completely secure. Likewise, unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time.

### Consent

When you use our Website or purchase our products or services, you acknowledge that you consent to the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time.  Use of information we collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will post such changes on our Website and/or send you an email. You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the Website after such changes have been posted.

  * About
  * Latest Posts

### [Preetjyot](http://www.mylittlemuffin.com/)

Becoming a parent, flipped my world upside down, and there was no way I was going to miss the first laugh, the first word, the first step, or any milestone in between.Staying at home not only meant quality time with my daughter, but also allowed more time to do what I love…Pen my thoughts down on my blog.  
I strongly believe in breaking all the stereotype ways of parenting.   
For me parenting is all about love and fun. My girls and I believe in jamming out in the car, in dancing in the rains, and in miracles. We believe in smiling till our cheek hurt and laughing till our neighbours’ ears burst. Parenting definitely comes with loads of challenges,but trust me facing these challenges becomes much more easier by having a fun and a happy attitude towards it.

#### Latest posts by Preetjyot ([see all](http://mylittlemuffin.com/author/admin/))

### Comments

comments
